<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyFitness App</string>
    <string name="hint_userName">Username</string>
    <string name="hintPassword">Password</string>
    <string name="txtLogin">Login</string>
    <string name="txtNoAttempts">"No. of Incorrect Attempts: "</string>
    <string name="txtWelcome">"Welcome to our app"</string>
    <string name="txtTitleLogin">Login</string>
    <string name="txtSignUp">New User? Sign up here.</string>
    <string name="btnTextSignUp">Sign up</string>
    <string name="txtTitleRegister">Register a new account</string>
    <string name="hintFullName">Full Name</string>
    <string name="hintWeight">Enter your weight (in kg)</string>
    <string name="hintHeight">Enter your height (in cm)</string>
    <string name="txtRegister">Create an account</string>
    <string name="btnBack">Back to Login page</string>
    <string name="txtGoogleLogin">OR</string>
    <string name="btnLogOut">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="lookUpText">LookUp . . .</string>
    <string name="title_activity_background">FullscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="startBtn">Sign in</string>
    <string name="toolbar_Text">MyFitness</string>
    <string name="imgWorkoutWelcomepage">Motivation picture</string>
    <string name="btnBeginWorkOut">Click Here to Start Working Out</string>
    <string name="txtViewTitle">Fight Like a Warrior</string>
    <string name="imgViewLarge">It changes according to imges you select on the gridView</string>
    <string name="btnChooseTheBodyPart">Click Here to go to the specific exercises of choosen body parts</string>
    <string name="txtViewPressOnExercise">Press on The Exercise you want to workout</string>
    <string name="imgViewExercisesMenu" />
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_drawer">NavigationDrawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">User\'s Full Name</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Member</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Sign Out</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile Information</string>
    <string name="menu_workout">Workout plan</string>
    <string name="CableKneelingCrunch">Instructions\n
Preparation\n

Kneel below high pulley. Grasp cable rope attachment with both hands. Place wrists against head. Position hips back and flex hips, allowing resistance on cable pulley to lift torso upward so spine is hyperextended.

\nExecution\n

With hips stationary, flex waist so elbows travel toward middle of thighs. Return and repeat.

\nComments\n
Note movement occurs in waist, not hips. See Spot Reduction Myth. Hyperextension of spine at top of motion is achieved by anterior rotation of pelvis with flexed hips.></string>
    <string name="CableTwist">Instructions
Preparation

Grasp stirrup from shoulder height cable pulley with both hands. Step and turn lower body away from pulley until near arm is horizontal and straight. Position feet wide apart facing away from pulley, furthest foot further away from pulley. Raise heel of nearest foot off floor. Bend knees of both legs slightly. Place far hand over other hand or interlace fingers.

Execution

Keeping arms straight, rotate torso to opposite side until cable makes contact with shoulder. Return to original position and repeat. Continue with opposite side.

Comments
Both arms should be horizontal and straight. This movement arguably involves more hip internal rotation and transverse adduction than spinal rotation. Although it is considered oblique movement, remarkably little rotation actually occurs through spine, although rotators of spine act largely as stabilizers except at very beginning and end of motion where resistance from cable is minimal.

A large part of rotational force actually occurs through rotation/transverse adduction of forward hip. Because rear leg is only supported by forefoot, hip of forward leg is utilized much greater than hip of rear leg since forward leg offers more secured base of support. Continued rotation would occur through spine except when cable makes contact with body precluding further movement and resistance would no longer be provided through cable since line of force is no longer perpendicular line of pull. Seated oblique exercises or those exercises where hips are stabilized allow for greater range of movement through spine. See Spot Reduction Myth.</string>
</resources>